It's not over. I'm not done. I will be the Wizard King.
The Wizard King? You're joking.
The thing is, these chains can measure the magic power of anyone they come in contact with,
and you have none. Not a single drop.
You were probably born that way.
I guess this explains why you didn't get a grimoire.
To possess not the slightest bit of magic in a world where magic is everything?
Why, that makes you a rare and precious bird indeed!
If that's true, then...
No matter how hard I push myself, I'll never be able to use magic.
You know I really can't think of anything more pitiful.
Forget about becoming the Wizard King. You'll be lucky to just get a job.
I bet your friend the genius over there is having a good laugh at your expense right about now.
Yeah, maybe...
You know so great the four-leaf clover chose him.
Then there's me.
This world is no use for someone like you, a poor magicless fool.
You might as well give it all up right now.
You were born a loser, you worthless runt!
Yeah, he's right.
No matter how hard I try, I guess there are some things that just aren't possible.
So, I might as well give...
Hey!
Who are you calling a loser?
Asta, it's true that you aren't going to become the Wizard King. Not ever.
You hear that? Even your little friend knows that it's impossible.
That's because I am going to be the Wizard King!
What?
You're wrong about Asta, Revji.
Very wrong.
Asta's no loser. He's my rival!
Huh?
This is who you would claim as your rival? The only person in the world without magic?
You.
Get off of me!
Sorry you had to see me at such a weak moment, you know.
Just... give me a second.
That's all! Then I'll destroy this guy!
You.
Is that... a Grim War?
I knew it.
Like you wouldn't be chosen, Asta.
There's no way.
This is what you've always done.
You have a way of making the impossible possible.
Now.
And back then.
I'm gonna be the Wizard King!
I'll keep you and everybody else safe.
No more worrying about food or money.
You'll have everything you ever wanted.
I'll prove it.
I'll show them all.
Show them?
Prove what?
That even if you're poor,
a commoner and an orphan,
you can still become the Wizard King.
The Wizard King
Who knows the Wizard King
And let's see what the name promises
In this morning
I don't think it's alright
Al Jiwon
Hopefully I know
But I never did I love it
I wish I could
No
Did you wait for me to lose myников
I?
Wait up!
Ah, ugh!
Ah, yuno!
Oh, jeez, are you okay?
Want a hand?
Yeah, thank you.
Sheesh. You're such a crybaby sometimes.
I know.
Come on, you're gonna be okay.
You know I've always got your back, right?
Yeah.
Okay, let's get going then.
They're all waiting for us up top.
This bread is yummy.
Yummy, but a bit hard, maybe?
Amazing, Sister Lily!
You're the best cook and awesomest baker ever!
Hey, when I grow up, we should get married and you can cook for me.
Actually, father's the one who baked that.
So maybe you should marry him.
Nuh-uh! He's gross!
I want to marry you, Sister, not some old man!
Sister!
Marry, marry, marry me!
That's a good boy, Osta.
I'm telling you, it'll never work.
She can't marry.
She's, um...
Sister Lily is a woman of the cloth.
I'm not giving up!
I'll keep asking her till I'm old and gray!
She'll say yes eventually!
Well, good luck.
And so, a deep, cold, and seemingly endless darkness covered the world.
It was on the brink of being destroyed by a ruthless demon.
That demon's a jerk!
But then, one brave mage stepped forward.
Whoa!
Hoping to dispel the darkness and bring Dawn to the world, he battled the demon.
Finally, he defeated the foul creature.
And when he was finished, the world was a brighter place than it had ever been before.
The long night ended at last, because the mage had brought Dawn to the world.
Hooray!
The triumphant mage was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Wow, the Wizard King?
Peace and prosperity reigned.
Hey, sister!
There's still one now, right?
A Wizard King, I mean.
Yes.
That role is one of the most vital in the kingdom.
The duty has been passed down throughout the ages, from one Wizard King to the next.
With the power of his magic to protect us, we live in relative safety.
It's because of the Wizard King that the Clover Kingdom is so peaceful.
Oh, wow!
So, he's a really important person?
Yes.
Second only to our nation's king.
Huh.
All right!
It's settled.
What do you mean?
What's settled?
I'm gonna be the Wizard King!
Sister?
Sorry, I'm surprised, that's all.
So, where did this come from?
Well, he beat that demon, didn't he?
So, he's way strong, and he's super cool, too!
I want to be just like him when I grow up.
And that's not all.
He's important.
The Wizard King has power.
And that means I can make all of your lives better.
Think about it.
Wearing nice clothes, filling up on as much food as you want?
I'll rebuild the church!
Yeah!
I'll fix this crumbling dump!
No, don't call it that.
Just wait, sister!
You'll be living the high life!
Well, that sounds wonderful.
Right, you know?
The Wizard King.
I'm gonna be important when I grow up!
I'll be the Wizard King!
So you should marry me!
Those two subjects are entirely unrelated.
I won't give up!
I'm not done!
Yes, you are.
Not done!
Very done.
I don't understand what's wrong with me!
No matter how hard I try, I still can't use any magic!
Let me help, sister.
I can hang the laundry up to dry for you.
Thank you, that would be very helpful.
Okay!
So you'll make...
I won't.
Me?
No way.
Still no.
I'm begging you, please marry me!
It's not going to help if you start crying too.
But poor Nash.
He...
He seems so upset.
Wait!
Let me take care of it!
Okay?
I mean, I'm gonna be the Wizard King, right?
Calling down a baby or two's gotta be a piece of cake compared to that.
Now hand him over!
Hush, now!
You're okay!
There's nothing for you to cry about!
I swear!
Everything is totally awesome!
There, there, little one.
Whoa!
Way to go, Wizard King!
That was impressive!
Aw, you shut up!
Down we go!
Sorry, I need to borrow one of the youngsters to run an errand for me.
Me, me, me, me!
I'll do it, Father!
I need this letter delivered to the village chief.
It shouldn't take too long.
Me, me, me, me!
It's a very important letter.
Me, me, me, me, me, me!
Could you deliver it for me, Yuma?
What?
Me, why?
Like I said, it's a very important letter.
I'm worried about trusting it to Asta.
Please just do it!
I have to meet with the chief of the neighboring village.
We won't make it through the winter unless we can get some food from them.
Our stores are low.
The pot potatoes are especially low.
I'll go.
You can just stay here.
Father's giving me this responsibility.
So, I'm going to take it.
Are you sure?
You'll be okay?
Of course, I'll be fine.
I won't be long.
Well, come on.
Don't just stand there.
There's firewood to chop.
And if you can't do magic, we might as well put you to use for manually.
Yeah, and what have you done today?
Have you haven't dug up the pot potatoes?
I finished doing that hours ago.
Look at that sky.
It'll be a cold one tonight.
I've had enough!
You're not welcome here anymore!
What do you think you're doing?
If you're going to keep drinking, then you'd best be ready to pay.
Not in the habit of giving out freebies, pal.
I don't know why anyone would want to drink in this dump anyway!
Dammit.
Whoa, stood up too fast.
I should be more careful.
The snow's really piling up.
Great, thank you very much.
You can tell the priest that you successfully delivered his message.
Yes, sir.
I should be heading back now.
It's getting late.
Be careful out there in the dark, son.
I will be.
Thank you, sir.
I'm sorry.
It's late.
I wonder where Yuno is.
I'm starving to death here.
Father hasn't returned from the other village, either.
Why can't we just eat without them?
You should be worrying about Yuno, not your stupid stomach!
Yeah, yeah.
Give that back to me.
It's mine.
Not anymore.
I'll get a nice chunk of change for this.
Give me back my...
Shut up!
Respect your betters, you brat.
Filth like you doesn't deserve something as fine as this.
Just give...
it back.
It's mine.
Give it back.
You've got to be kidding.
Am I supposed to be intimidated by the puny urchin and his puny spell?
You fight me with that, and you die.
Yuno!
Another brat!
That belongs to Yuno!
Give it back!
Give it back right now!
Get your filthy little hands off of me!
Damn it!
Stupid twerp!
I'm not done with you yet, jerk!
Hey!
I'm still not done!
Stupid little bugger!
Still not done!
I'm not done yet!
What the hell?
Damn brat wouldn't give up.
I've got better things to do.
Asta!
I'm so sorry.
It's my fault.
I should have...
Come on, don't sweat it.
It's like I said.
I've always got your...
back.
You know that.
Asta?
This is what you've always done.
You have a way of making the impossible possible.
But you don't have any magic!
How could you get a grimoire?
And that sword!
What kind of freak of nature are you?
You took my spell and turned it...
into your magic power?
Even without traditional magic power,
I will be the Wizard King!
My magic is never giving up!
I've always figured if I can't use magic,
I always figured if I can't use magic, at least I can use my body.
I trained to build up strength and it looks like it's finally paid off.
Asta.
Asta, hang in there. I'm sorry. It's all my fault. I'm so sorry.
This? Please, don't worry about it. This is nothing. After all, I'm gonna be the Wizard King, right?
I'm gonna be the Wizard King. I'll keep you and everybody else safe.
No more worrying about food or money. You'll have everything you ever wanted.
I'll prove it. I'll show them all.
Show them? Prove what?
That even if you're poor, a commoner and an orphan, you can still become the Wizard King.
You really think so?
Yeah.
Commoners? Orphans?
Anybody can do it. As long as they're willing to work hard.
Anybody?
Even me. And even you.
I… I'm never going to cry again. I've decided.
What do you mean?
I'll do it, too. I'm going to become the Wizard King.
I'll work hard and get strong so I can protect you and everybody else.
I'll do whatever it takes.
And I'll never give up.
Check it out, you know. I got a snazzy new grimoire.
Okay, it's a little beat up, but I'll treasure it all my life anyway.
I will.
Well, you saved me yet again.
I will repay my debt one day.
Asta, we made a promise. Do you remember it?
So you want to be the Wizard King, too?
That means, you know.
Asta, you are my rival!
I actually can't believe you remember it.
The way you've been acting lately, I was pretty sure you'd forgotten.
Like I'd be friendly with someone I consider my rival.
You showed me it was possible.
Gave me hope.
That even though we're poor orphans, commoners,
we can still make something of ourselves in this world.
And to prove that?
To make Sister Lily and everybody else happy.
We'll fight to see who will be the Wizard King.
Whatever it takes.
誰もここから出られない
閉じた狭い教室で
今日も主役が輝いた
僕は眩しくて目を閉じる
散々考えた革命は手の中に
おかしいだろう
笑いたければ笑えばいいから
残された僕らは
何かになりたくて
いつまでも
同じ朝を迎えてる
明日を選ぶのは
君自身しかいらないよ
これ程度
今日までの僕らを
喰あ
ご視聴ありがとうございました
So what if I can't use magic?
I'm still gonna join a Magic Knight squad and become the Wizard King!
Black Clover, page 3.
To the Royal Capital!
My magic is never giving up!
Black Clover, page 3.
One Woman's
A